>Typesetting
--Ep Title
Episode 56
Tokyo Colony No. 1, Part 3
--Uhh
Um... Well...
Uh... See...
--Sure-Hit
Sure-Hit,
Sure-Kill
Sure-Hit
--Sumo
You'll lose if you
go out of bounds.
Same if anything but your
soles touches the ground.
Huh?
Seriously?
--Top text
Silence
Confession
Denial
--Bottom text (2)
Itadori: No!
Itadori: I just went to the bathroom
Higuruma: So you did enter it, then!
Itadori: Y-Yes...
Itadori: I'm sorry...
--Bottom text
Guilty
Confiscation
--Office
Higuruma Law Office
Guilty
Confiscation
Death Penalty
Executioner's Sword
--Rule 10
Players shall be able to view the following information on other players:
name, points, number of rules added, and current colony.
Players may transfer a number of points of their choosing to another player.
--Next Ep
Next Episode
Tokyo Colony No. 1, Part 4